[PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Ah. (In Korean) Hello , Mr.--
Jeon...
Oh.
Um...
Here's your suit, sir.
- (In Korean) Thank you.
- Of course, sir.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- What were you doing?!
- Ouch, ma'am!
- This is a respectable hotel!
- Ma'am, please, it hurts!
I wasn't doing anything, ma'am!
What do you mean
you weren't doing anything?!
You've got a lot of nerve,
don't you?
You're a whore!
- Whore!
- Ma'am...
how could you say that to me?
Why can't you just call it...
customer service instead?
[GASPS] Don't get smart with me!
[SLAPS]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
You know what...
you flirting around is grounds
for termination.
Ma'am, I wasn't flirting around.
And why would I flirt around
with Mr. Jeon?
I mean, it's obvious from
his skincare routine alone
that they’d never
go for someone like me.
And you even have the nerve
to crack jokes right now?
Do you want to get slapped again
so you'll finally straighten up?
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Not while I'm here.
[ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYING]